charging occurring he did have some um
you know all this happening and he did
have all this coming out of the cell so
it's doing a multiples at the present
moment how would those discount drop s
drop s initially wrong
s so others would put their live cut but
within it within it what's actually
occurring is that um instead of what
he's got multiples occurring here this
is water you just took off yeah that
came straight out of the salt any see
what's on the surface of this water
around the ring compared to any of these
others what's at here for
nowadays what's that white stuff around
these
sides we need glasses put the glasses on
the
camera stop shaking yeah anybody see
them nobody's
answering bubbles they bubbles oh yeah
oh right actually it does look a bit
like youron doesn't it
you're really taking the piss out of me
now AR you they um they're Bubbles and
those bubbles are actually coming out of
the water and being produced as as a
Charged
gas okay same as what's in themselves
and this cell here produces those kind
of Bubbles as well even when there's no
power put into this for hours and hours
then it'll slowly fade off so all these
other effects in there are actually
bleeding the charge what cake bottle
there they're not they're still there
yeah the which one the black one this
one yeah okay this this stuffing
it top
andot it's the same material if you want
to send it it was here the other day too
you've got most of it on the bottom but
you got some on the top and so on if you
going to have that analyze the stuff on
the top and the stuff on the bottom is
different but soon as that stuff on the
top you can discharge the surface or it
will discharge itself and fall through
the lab will tell you it's the same
stuff it's just the only thing
separating those two at the moment
because of identical stuff is charge so
you've got in the bottom and some
in the top and clean in the middle
um this one here has got most all the
gone out of it but it's locked in a
yellow acidy stuff this one here is a
different material again and everything
else and if you looking there there's
layers of
it different layers and we shake this
one again just for them you're going to
do that so that's all
again but this look across the surf look
across the surface now this is already
done but for these people here look
across the surface she's clearing again
this has got the memory of don't have me
in here anymore yeah drop me out please
and this water here doesn't help this no
but this water here is cleaning itself
see the camera probably pick it up now
and everything pass it around if you
like don't Stir It Up again but we have
probably that far now already started
clearing yeah you can see it okay she'll
clear clear pretty quickly over against
the window
okay no it's still
probably the day film you got on the
camera the other day and we just H it
in now some it'll fall out and then this
black stuff this black stuff here and
everything else
is and that stirred up and everything
else and um and you can see it all
sticking some of the particle sticking
on the sides and we just sit that down
and everything else and and that'll
clear like it did the other day and this
one
here w't it will there's still plenty of
guns in that yet yeah on the B it's a
little bit stuck to the bottom okay but
that that um won't change color back to
clean water it started its life with
spring
water that
water so it's meant to be clone so the
scum around the cell just gets r
generated into the water and regenerated
as a form of memory till you get bottles
of it like
that yep it'll keep pulling down like in
here um in here that ring around there
and everything else um it's a rubber one
m and that one there you can see a black
mark in there and it's coming off on
your fingers that rubber in there or
whatever it is is breaking down so it's
going to make some of this Mark as well
um so that rubber could be some of the
black which is on the surface okay or
the bottom doesn't matter um it makes a
hell of a lot or and the wells and
everything else top where it's been
ground in the bottom where we can't even
see at the moment and around here is
making some more of it so um it just
keeps making it and breaking down you'll
never get rid of it okay because you got
wrong material in there if you were
doing hydrogen and oxygen and everything
else with two rods if that's what you
were chasing me you can pump thousands
of volts into here and everything else
your water stays clean you don't get
into this happening um in fact to make
hydrogen oxygen it actually wants more
and more electrolyte or in it to
conduct more really the trouble in um
cutting the tubes if one were to snap
freeze the tubes and then cut them
slowly do you think that would get
around the they drop them in liquid
nitrogen and then go to cut them don't
know don't know why somebody play with
that and find out yeah yeah um see I
haven't played every single thing you
know um but you're going to find if
you're playing with different cells and
different stuff everything El you're
going to find multiples of different
things happening yeah don't think that
your cell told these guys yesterday
don't think that your cell is limited to
doing one thing don't expect it just to
to you want it to do one thing this is
going to do multiples of things thing is
this is producing a gas if you want it
has an explosion gas if you have that
but it also produces implosive that's I
want that
culprit another thing it does is it it
um it'll clean up water it'll whatever's
in water it'll clean up the other thing
it does is it pulls the rubbers to
pieces or pulls the metal to pieces if
you like pulling things a pieces that's
great okay and um if you um if you find
out it's charging this water and putting
a memory into the water so any what
comes off and everything else it is
self- sustaining cleaning now we can see
oh yeah yeah can take that to the camera
without into the light can you Shing
shaking it's falling out
so
that the has a
yellow right this one here is quicker
specific gravity see the black is
quicker the black is thicker you can see
the RAM and Coke in
that that's clearing very fast